slidebean.com 2019-07-30

# Privacy Policy | Slidebean

Last updated: January 25, 2019

Previous version  
[  
‍](http://templates.slidebean.com/terms-legacy)  
This Privacy Policy explains Slidebean Inc’s (“Slidebean” or “we” or “our”) privacy practices for visitors to our proprietary Internet site at www.slidebean.com (the “Website”). We created this Privacy Policy to explain what information we gather from you when you visit our Website and how we may use and disclose this information. 

This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and made a part of Slidebean’s Terms of Use.You, our clients are our main driver and we value you and the information you trust us as a user. At Slidebean Inc., we wish to acknowledge our true and honest commitment to your individual right to data and privacy protection. In an effort to outline how we handle information obtained, we share with you our Privacy Policies.

Slidebean Inc., is committed to keeping any and all personal information collected of those individuals that visit our website and make use of our online facilities and services accurate, confidential, secure and private. Our privacy policy has been designed and created to ensure those affiliated with of our commitment and realization of our obligation not only to meet but to exceed most existing privacy standards.

By using our Website, you consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. If we make any material changes to our Privacy Policy, we will post a new policy on the Website and update the “last updated” date set forth above. Policy changes will apply only to information collected after the date of the change.

This Privacy Policy applies only to information collected through our Website and not to information collected offline.

Withdrawal of consent hereunder. You may at any time withdraw a consent granted hereunder by contacting us and stating so. In case of withdrawal, Slidebean will not process Personal Data subject to this consent any longer unless legally required to do so.

 **HOW DO WE USE YOUR INFORMATION?**

Slidebean may collect and may make use of personal information to assist in the operation of our website and to ensure delivery of the services you need and request.  The use of information collected is to personalize your experience, to improve the website, and customer service, to administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature, to process your transactions, to ask for ratings and reviews of services or products, to follow up with you after correspondence (live chat, email or phone inquiries), to send periodic emails.

At times, we may find it necessary to use personally identifiable information as a means to keep you informed of other possible products and/or services, through our emails, news, blog, videos and downloads, that may be available to you. Slidebean may also be in contact with you with regards to completing surveys and/ or research questionnaires related to your opinion of current or potential future services may be offered. Your data may be shared with the services listed in this link: [http://templates.slidebean.com/gdpr-data](https://slidebean.com/gdpr-data). These services allow Slidebean to access data from your Slidebean account on a third-party service and perform actions with it.

Slidebean can disclose your personal information, without prior notice to you, only if required to do so in accordance with applicable laws and/or in a good faith belief that such action is deemed necessary or is required in an effort to:

1\. Remain in conformance with any decrees, laws or statues or in an effort to comply with any process which may be served, upon and/ or our website;  
2\. Maintain, safeguard and/or preserve all the rights and/or property of: and  
3\. Perform under demanding conditions in an effort to safeguard the personal safety of users of and/or general public.

It comes to the collection of personal information from children under the age of 16 years old, the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, United States’ consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children’s privacy and safety online.

We do not specifically market to children under the age of 16 years old.

‍

This Privacy Policy explains Slidebean Inc’s (“Slidebean” or “we” or “our”) privacy practices for visitors to our proprietary Internet site at www.slidebean.com (the “Website”). We created this Privacy Policy to exIn the first interaction with Slidebean, when you become our customer by signing up for our services, we become a data controller of your Personal Data. Our general terms and our privacy policy states exactly what we do with your data for this interaction, we can guarantee that we will **control your personal data** in a GDPR (General Data Protection Regulation) compliant manner and that we have signed data processing agreements with so that your data is also **processed** in a GDPR compliant manner.

In accordance to the new General Data Protection Regulation our [Presentation Insights](http://templates.slidebean.com/presentation-insights/) feature allows the presentation owner to collect data on who sees the deck, EU viewers will now need to **consent for their data to be tracked** on this feature. Presentation owners whom are sharing a deck with viewers in the EU, will be **required to allow the viewer to provide or deny consent** if they wish to be compliant with the GDPR legislation.

When you start using our services as a presentation owner in our Presentation Insight services and, most likely, store your customers personal data in our services we have a second relationship. This time around, you are the data controller of your customers data and Slidebean Inc becomes a data processor of said data. For this interaction, we can guarantee that we will **process customers personal data** in a GDPR compliant manner. However you will be responsible of acting as data controller in a GDPR compliant manner.

For more information about compliance with GDPR Regulation by Slidebean Inc. go to: [https://slidebean.com/gdpr/](http://templates.slidebean.com/gdpr/)

 **DO WE DISCLOSE THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT TO OUTSIDE PARTIES?**

We do not sell to, trade with or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information unless we provide you with advance notice and consent, except as described herein. The term "outside parties" does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our Website, conducting our business or servicing you, as long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential.

In the event that we sell our company, or otherwise transfer any assets of our company, we may provide your information to the purchaser so that you may continue the relationship or business with us and our products. We may also release your information when we believe that release is necessary to comply with law, enforce the policies of our Website or protect our or others' rights, property or safety.

However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising or other uses.

Our site allows third-party behavioral tracking.

In accordance to the new General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) our [Presentation Insights](http://templates.slidebean.com/presentation-insights/) feature allows the presentation owner to collect data on who sees the deck, EU viewers will now need to **consent for their data to be tracked** on this feature. Presentation owners whom are sharing a deck with viewers in the EU, will be **required to allow the viewer to provide or deny consent** if they wish to be compliant with the GDPR legislation.

‍

When sharing a presentation, you'll now see a new toggle **('Enable GDPR compliance')** to let your viewers to allow/reject tracking of their viewing of the presentation.

 **  
DO WE USE COOKIES?**

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if this is enabled on the browser itself) Cookies enable the site's or service provider’s systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about traffic and interactions on the Website so that we can offer better experiences and tools on the Website in the future.  
‍  
We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding the visitors to our Website. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser’s (i.e., Google Chrome or Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser’s Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. If you disable cookies, you may not have access to many features that streamline your experience on our Website, and some of our services may not function properly.

 **SAFEGUARDING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

We take every precaution to maintain adequate physical, procedural and technical security with respect of our offices and information of the user’s personal information under our control, we implement security measures when a user enters, submits or accesses information or places an order.

Our website is scanned on a regular basis for security holes or known vulnerabilities in compliance with payment card industry and in order to make your visit to our site as safe as possible.

All identifiable information is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology, and we do not store sensitive information such as credit card information on our servers, we use payment gateway provider.

However, no commercial method of information transfer over the Internet or electronic data storage is known to be 100% secure; therefore, we encourage you should always take care to safeguard your personal information.

Our users will be notified within 72 hours if a Data breach occurs.

 **WHAT SHOULD YOU CONSIDER BEFORE CLICKING ON THIRD PARTY LINKS?**

This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by our Website. In an attempt to provide you with increased value, we may include third party links on our Website. These linked websites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked websites. ). We encourage all users and visitors to be aware when they leave our website and to read privacy policies of each website that collects personally identifiable information. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our Website and welcome any feedback about these linked websites (including if a specific link does not work). 

**WHERE DO I DIRECT QUESTIONS ABOUT THIS PRIVACY POLICY?**

We welcome your questions, comments and concerns about our Privacy Policy. Please send us all feedback pertaining to this Privacy Policy to privacy@slidebean.com

 **WHAT ARE MY CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS?**

Under California’s “Shine the Light” law, California residents who provide personal information in obtaining services for personal, family or household use are entitled to request and obtain from us once per calendar year information about the customer information that we shared, if any, with other businesses for their own direct marketing uses. If applicable, this information would include the categories of customer information and the names and addresses of those businesses with which we shared customer information for the calendar year previous to such request (e.g. requests made in 2014 will receive information regarding 2013 sharing activities).

To obtain this information from us, please send an email message to privacy@slidebean.com with “Request for California Privacy Information” in the subject line and in the body of your message. We will then email you the requested information. Not all information sharing is covered by the “Shine the Light” requirements and only information on covered sharing will be included in our response.
